<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Jekyll Bootstrap</title>
 <link href="http://username.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://username.github.io"/>
 <updated>2015-09-21T13:31:37-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://username.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Name Lastname</name>
   <email>blah@email.test</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Job search strategy</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/job/2015/09/21/job-search-strategy"/>
   <updated>2015-09-21T04:21:14-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/job/2015/09/21/job-search-strategy</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Now that I’ve spoken to several companies about web developer jobs, it’s clear the market is more competitive than I originally estimated. I’ve been dead-set against pursuing internships or volunteer opportunities in favor of a full-time (&lt;em&gt;paid&lt;/em&gt;) role. I plan to maintain that strategy for as long as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now I’ve been fiddling with this blog and my GitHub Pages stuff in general.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Reset, all over again</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/jekyll/github/2015/09/19/jekyll-reset-again"/>
   <updated>2015-09-19T16:36:34-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/jekyll/github/2015/09/19/jekyll-reset-again</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I feel like I finally have a grip on Jekyll as it runs in GitHub Pages. It took several attempts to install the Jekyll engine (parser) inside the existing directory and setup, but it seems to be working. I had to delete the Pages directory a couple times and it looks like I lost some update counts. But whatevs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The challenge will be updates as they use a fairly manual template process.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Still on the lookout</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/job/2015/09/17/summer"/>
   <updated>2015-09-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/job/2015/09/17/summer</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Summer is drawing to a close here in Portland, and I’m still looking for work. I had a good month of job search once my code class was done. But no solid offers came from it. So I’ll continue the search.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon I’ll likely expand the job search from just developer positions to include web producer and project manager gigs. I’m still determined to be a developer but I’m also sensitive to the fact that I need steady work. The sooner the better. I hope it all works out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Jekyll is now running</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/general/2015/09/17/hello-world"/>
   <updated>2015-09-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/general/2015/09/17/hello-world</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I recently installed the Jekyll blog engine on my GitHub Pages site. All good so far but the configuration is going to take some time.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Panic!</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/general/2015/05/27/panic"/>
   <updated>2015-05-27T14:17:09-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/general/2015/05/27/panic</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today several of us from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.portlandcodeschool.com&quot;&gt;Portland Code School&lt;/a&gt; took a tour of &lt;a href=&quot;http://panic.com/&quot;&gt;Panic Software&lt;/a&gt;. We do about one tour a week and this one was pretty unique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, Panic is the first company we toured where I’m a customer. I’ve been a long-time Transmit FTP user. Plus I’ve become a bit of a Coda fan lately. First class software all around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, this was the first pure software business we’ve seen. It’s not an agency or coders-for-hire outfit. They build their own stuff and sell it for a living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most-interesting thing about Panic is their absolute lack of employee turnover. They only have about 15 employees to begin with. And the fellow speaking today said they’ve only had two departures in his tenure (since 2011).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today’s tech market, that’s absolutely tremendous. I guess it shows that if you take care of your employees, you don’t have to deal with turnover.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>More fish, please</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/diet/2015/05/27/more-fish-please"/>
   <updated>2015-05-27T09:47:17-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/diet/2015/05/27/more-fish-please</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Over the years, my wife and I got into the habit of eating most meals separately. The idea evolved from Ann’s dietary needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She eats pretty healthy. I usually piece together what I can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we returned to the Pacific Northwest - with both of us being around the house more - we have started eating a lot of fresh fish. Salmon and steelhead in particular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite thing about salmon is that it requires very little help. You bake for 10-15 minutes and send it straight to the plate with no need for oil or sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pair it with some green beans and garlic toast and you have my go-to meal for 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My resume</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/general/2015/05/27/resume"/>
   <updated>2015-05-27T04:25:09-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/general/2015/05/27/resume</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’ve been playing around with static site generators. Since I’m already using GitHub and Pages it seemed only logical that I use for testing. Jekyll is pretty straightforward so far. Let’s see how I can make this easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, here’s my resume:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curt Poff
Portland Oregon
(510) 229-­7964&lt;br /&gt;
curt.poff@gmail.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt;
I’m an ambitious problem solver who is new to the programming game. I’m still refining my code skills, but I bring 15 years of professional Web production experience. I’m a reliable, ambitious problem solver who is looking for a front-end developer potion with a great company. Preferably one that puts value in having fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CRITICAL SKILLS&lt;/strong&gt;
—Proficient in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript (Node, Angular), Bootstrap, text editors and packages/plug-ins/tools, Git, Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop), Web analytics (Omniture SiteCatalyst, Google). I also have extensive experience using database-­driven content management systems and Agile project management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;
Student - Full Stack Javascript Immersion program
Portland Code School, present - Aug. 2015 —Over 500 hours of hands-on experience, building full-stack web applications with JavaScript using Node.js, MVC framework, and Test-Driven Development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Producer - Interactive
Walmart.com, San Bruno, Calif., Jan. 2013 - Nov. 2014 —Senior member of the web producer team in the Creative department in the Walmart.com Customer Experience group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online Managing Editor, Senior Web Producer, Product Manager
Macworld/PCWorld, San Francisco, Calif., Feb. 2005 - Jan. 2013 —Owned and managed all editorial products (home pages, index and article pages), publishing platform (CMS), and live events through the entire product lifecycle. Moved from a position where I launched and maintained core editorial products, into one where I was responsible the overall success of the entire editorial product line.
—Recipient of the 2008 Macworld/PCWorld Leadership Award.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online Editor
Arizona Republic, Phoenix Ariz., Aug. 2001 - Feb. 2005&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web Producer
KGW ­ NewsChannel 8, Portland Ore., April 2000 - June 2001&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;
B.S. in History, Portland State University&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introduction</title>
   <link href="http://username.github.io/general/2015/05/27/introduction"/>
   <updated>2015-05-27T04:25:09-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://username.github.io/general/2015/05/27/introduction</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We’ve been playing around with static site generators. Since I’m already using GitHub and Pages it seemed only logical that I use for testing. Jekyll is pretty straightforward so far. Let’s see how I can make this easier.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
